Will this fit?
これ入るかな?
Thank you very much for coming.
い っぱ い来てくれてありがとう
I think I'm going to go in.
入っちゃいそう
This doesn't fit, right?
入らないんだよね、これ
Sorry.
ごめんね
Please, tell me you can go.
お願いだから行っていいよって言って
You can go.
行っていいよ
And then, wait, I think it's going to go crazy.
そしたら待って、めちゃめちゃ行くと思う
Ah, where is it?
あー、どこや
It's still in.
まだ入ってる
show?
見せる?
I can't see it.
見えないね
ah,
あー、
It also includes things that I'm used to.
慣 れたことも入ってる
Oh, what is this?
あー、なんだこれ
I can't get in.
入らない
Will everything fit?
全部入るかな?
I don't know if it all goes in.
全部入るとわかんないよ
It's a little tight though.
ちょっときついんだけど
This is terrible.
やばいよ
I want to go home even if it's just a hole.
穴でも帰りたいな
I didn't do it in that hole.
その穴でしてないよ
It's my first time today.
今日初めてだよ
Look at that pussy Emi just mentioned.
えのみの言ったばっかのマンコ見てください
I really went there.
めっちゃ行っちゃった
This is what my nose looks like.
鼻はこんな感じだよ
I can still do it.
まだまだできるよ
I'm thinking of doing it until about 10 o'clock.
10時くらいまでやりたいなと思ってるよ
Take a break.
ちょっと休憩
I'll drink tea.
お茶飲むね
And drinking tea.
お茶飲むのと
I'll just wash it by hand.
ちょっとお手で洗ってくるよ
What is your anal experience?
アナルの経験は?
Yes.
ありまーす
Awesome.
すげー
A bag please.
バッグでお願いします
Was your nose cute?
鼻可愛かった?
More please.
もっとお願い
I want to put it in.
入れたいね
In a bag.
バ ッグで
After doing this, I'll wash my hands.
これしたら手洗ってくる
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I'll go wash my hands.
手洗ってくるね
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててね
I'm home.
ただいま
I want to do another 20 minutes.
あと20分くらいやりたいな
Can you still go?
まだいける?
Welcome back.
おかえり
I was lonely.
寂しかったよ
It's about 30 seconds.
30秒くらいだよ
Were you lonely?
寂しかった?
I want to see the push again.
推しをもう一回見たいな
I want to wipe it again too.
私ももう一回拭きたい
This is what my hometown looks like.
地元はこんな感じです
It's okay.
やえばです
Don't you stream cosplay?
コ スプレ配信はしてないの?
I've never done it and I don't have anything.
したことないし、なんも持ってないんだよね
What do you want me to do?
何してほしい?
Suppose I do cosplay.
コスプレやるとする
Then.
したら
The Sunbai bag looks like this.
スンバイバッグはこんな感じで
I would like you to distribute uniforms.
制服配信してほしい
Mouth and nose at the same time, just for a moment.
口元、鼻同時で一瞬だけ
It's really a moment.
本当に一瞬だよ
I won't do it again.
もうしない
absolute.
絶対
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's too cute.
可愛すぎです
thank you.
ありがとう
I'm only 20 years old.
まだ20歳だからね
It's not the salty way though.
塩かり方じゃないけど
There's going to be a lot of salt.
めっちゃ塩出るよ
There's already a lot of salt coming out.
塩はもう、めちゃめちゃ出るよ
Should I use more salt?
もっと塩拭いちゃっていいかな?
最後
What's it like when you go with anal?
オナルで行くときってどんな感じ?
I don't really understand things anymore.
もうなんか、よくわかんなくなっちゃうよね
Something.
なんか
This area is starting to go crazy.
この辺がウォーってなっちゃう
amazing.
すごい
Sorry I was just talking most of the time.
今ほとんど喋ってたのに、ごめんね
About 160 people watched it.
160人くらい見てくれて
Finally, let's break through this perception.
最後、こちらのみなしを吹き抜けて
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Feels good.
気持ちいい
If you want to avoid it, please do it.
避けちゃうなら、やってほしい
I've been there four or five times already, but if you'd like, let's go together.
もう4、5回行っちゃったけど、よかったら一緒に行きましょう
It's my first time here.
初めて来ました
I can't look forward to next time.
次回楽しみに取れない
thank you.
ありがとう
I went there while looking at Minami's face.
みなみの顔見ながら行って
Ordinary times.
普通の時
Probably when I was 18 years old.
18歳の時かな
Chenchen please.
チェンチェンください
Give me some cock milk.
チンポミルクちょうだい
please.
お願い
Chincheng Markli
チンチェンマークリ
ー.
ー
Let's take advantage of it.
コ トクにしよう
Put out a lot of flavor.
コトクいっぱい出して
It was amazing to see the number of people.
人数見たらすごい
287 people are watching.
287人も見てるよ
It's so hot that something like sperm comes out.
来 すぎて、なんか精子みたいなやつ出てくる
Look.
ほら
That's amazing.
すごいね
amazing.
すごい
I can fit a lot of fingers in it.
指いっぱい入るよ
Three?
3本?
My hands are sticky.
手がねちゃねちゃだよ
Yes, then the last one.
はい、じゃあ最後
I guess I'll finish with a cuppa.
クパンして終わろうかな
I wonder when the next one will be.
次はいつだろうな
10 How many days should I do it?
10何日間にやろうかな
11 or 12?
11か、12か
I guess that's about it.
そんくらいかな
Again, let's do it at this time as usual.
また、でも時間はいつも通りこの時間にやろう
From 8 o'clock.
8時から
I'm thinking of doing it from 8am to 10pm.
8時から10時くらいでやろうかなって思ってるよ
I basically don't do anything on days when I'm not streaming, but
配信しない日ものするの、基本的にはしないけど、
I'll do it if I can't take it anymore.
我慢できなくなったらしちゃうよ
I don't really like the build, so I might not get into it that much.
ビルドあんま好きじゃないから、そんなに入らないかもしれない
But.
けど
Like this.
こんな 感じで
So, is everyone ready?
では、みんなもういけた?
Properly.
ちゃんと
Lick it down.
下ペロペロして
I watched it from beginning to end.
最初から最後まで見ちゃったよ
Oh no.
やば
thank you.
ありがとう
I haven't gone yet.
まだいってない
Thank you.
ありがとうね
Well, I think it's time to take a shower.
では、そろそろシャワー浴びてこようと思います
I'm glad I got to do something anal today.
今日は何かアナルとかもやれてよかったなって感じ
I had a feeling.
気持ちがあった
Everyone, please come and see my pussy again.
みんな、おまんこまた見に来てね
bye bye.
バイバイ
See you soon.
またねー